But I think it is associated with community and joy.
And when you say something that offends someone, then it is a
Very strange kind of humor that only sick people laugh at.
Love.
Have you seen Katla?
Fucking fucking pussy.
There is no one who likes you.
I hope you die.
If you don't put down your blog and shut up,
Will I soon stand outside your door.
You will not be able to escape.
I will cut your throat and rape you with a damn baseball tree.
Cat ate bag.
SKET BACK!
Cute!
Sweet!
Can't you give it a little gravel so it gets stoned instead?
Morgan, what's wrong with you?
Millan will say nothing more.
She has put down her blog.
Huh, is that true?
Cruelly!
Why?
She should save some plague -infected young people in Africa.
What the hell do I know about it?
So damn King Morgan!
Should that also represent humor or?
Plague -infected children or you?
Hello?
And what the hell should a slant fucked fucking whore get lots of space,
On her blog just because she has a pussy between her legs.
Give the feminists a little more cock so maybe they are content!
You need to be penalized.
Whore!
One night we will stand outside your house.
Disgusting lodder.
Your oblique pussy.
You will die!
Negro ball is what it's called.
Surely I am not the one who has named it or?
Ignorant disgust!
You suck cock!
If you prefer to suck cock then it makes your fucking gay fucking!
Is married to you difference!
Learn Swedish if you are going to live here Blatte pussy.
Pussy!!
Someone should fuck you down your fucking disgust!
Someone should drive up a flag bar in the ass on you!
Wrong writing!
Your uneducated idiot!
Shut up on you pussy!
Fucking whore!
Whore!
Pussy!
Slut!
Ludder!
Die!